Yakup Onur Pirdal

Design and Configuration Engineer

Karşıyaka/İZMİR | +905057594060 | yonurpirdal@hotmail.com in linkedin.com/in/yakup-onur-pirdal-044a9346

Summary

Design and Configuration Engineer maintaininng, troubleshooting and designing navy combat management and firing system. Highly interested embedded system designs and developing software for embedded systems. Experiments worked in a system engineer team who supported and maintained a system which is based on Linux and Unix OS, being included in a research and development team which developed products using NI products Altium PCB design software.

Work experience

Design and Configuration Engineer

2012 - 2018

ARMERKOM

- Worked in a team design and configuration combat systems for 4 years
- Maintaining and troubleshooting systems which work on Linux & Unix OS.
- Including a team that develops a special project management system using Redmine.

Technical Support Staff

2011 - 2011

REYSA\$

Technical support, and configuration ZTE MSAN device for Türk Telekom A.Ş.

Education

Master Degree 2013 - 2018

Gebze Technical University

Developing a lithium-ion based battery management system.

Bachelor Degree 2004 - 2010

Süleyman Demirel University

Electronic and Communication Engineering

Core Competencies

- EmbeddedC
- PCB Design
- Linux & Unix System Engineering

Skills

Hardware/Systems

ST, TI, NXP, Microchip microcontrollers, PC/Server, Routers, Switches, IP Telephony, Unix(Solaris), Linux(Centos), Windows

Languages

C, PCB design, Unix, Linux

Applications

Keil MDK-5, SWSTM32, Altium and Mentor Graphics PCB design, Redmine, Microsoft Office Suite: Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint